by H.
Dance in the jungle I don't know
I don't know
Give me give me give me give me give me more
Oh yeah my life is like a drama
Yeah yeah
Dance in the jungle
I would like to perform.
Thank you very much.
What is your name?
Nacchan.
You're Nacchan, right?
What? Now?
Now?
Don't fix it.
I don't want to.
Stop it.
Yes, yes. Calm down.
This is my first time with Anpanman.
Let's go with power.
There were changes on stage between rehearsal and performance.
Yes, yes.
The position of the flag color.
Phew.
Like that.
It's reversed.
Ana and Yuzu are reversed.
Boring.
Huh?
Can I ask you to move one more time? It didn't stop, did it?
No, I didn't.
Here you go.
Let's see..,
Say, I think that Sayaka's getting cuter.
Why?
You mean she didn't?
I heard she wasn't.
No, it wasn't.
Micro Cyanide Roulette!
That's good. That's great. It's very exciting.
We have four microphones here.
There's our microphone,
Only one of these microphones can produce a proper voice.
I heard that the other microphones produce strange voices,
If you get the correct microphone, you get 2 points!
Thank you very much for this!
Hannah, I'll take this one!
My own microphone!
Yay!
I knew I'm a blue person.
It's my color.
I love mine!
Here I go!
This is Hana Kojima of Rainflash!
I bet you just changed it.
I'm pretty sure Hana was right originally.
There was a correct answer originally.
She's a Moeka guesser, so she's going to get it right.
I'll guess and get Moeka right!
Because you guessed Moeka.
Yuzu is like Takekusu's.
It's raining, but I don't think he'll make Moeka's mike look weird
I think that's the kind of uniform Takekku-san has.
So I'm going to go with yellow.
I'm Yuuki Ichikawa of Rain Flash
That was my voice, wasn't it?
That was my usual voice, wasn't it?
Yes, just right.
That's my usual voice, isn't it?
I get two points for that.
I have to do this all the time.
I know, I'm on the glass point now.
I don't know what to do.
But I recommend you to use Maeka's mike.
Why? I don't like it.
No, I don't like it.
But we don't have to go with Umami at all.
I'm going to go with Hana's mic.
Here we go.
Congratulations.
I wanted two points.
Next, though, Moka is going to win,
Make Leaner number 4.
Because Mr. Takeuchi did Moka anyway,
Maybe he has a mark on his eyebrows.
Or maybe all the voices are normal.
Or maybe they are all normal voices.
What?
They might all be normal voices.
Wow!
Yay!
We did it!
By the way, we are number 0 so far.
Then, I would like you to do your best for maximum victory, Moeka-san.
Then, I'll make my yellow.
The Amegrasch.
Poopoo!
Ah! That's not right! Already!Oh, no! That's not it! Oh, no!
It's complicated. It's Harakiri now, right?
They cut this kind of thing.
Our voices don't matter.
I'll do my best.
Let's practice.
I'll do my best
They'll cut our voices.
It's not important!
This is not important for a candy bar.
I know you're tired.
Let's go for it.
And let's eat a lot.
Have fun.
As always.
Concentrate
Let's go for it!
All you snipers out there
Let's go for it.
Let's go candy striping.
Let's go.
Ooh!
Mistfest is over!
That was fun!
Hey, it was so much fun.
I did Mistfest and Illyriibe, and it was a lot of fun,
I heard there is a final question here.
Okay, I'll read the final question.
This Bell, the festival venue, is a famous department store based in Nagoya.
What kind of department store?
I know.
Save!
What's that?
Is it west?
Marui!
Not at all.
Genta!
What?
I don't know.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
You were saying something, weren't you?
Round ball.
Ah, Tokyu.
Don't say two.
I wonder what it is.
Let's see, what was that?
Tokyu Hands.
A store!
Maybe...
Oh, yeah, I should say Ikira or something.
Zana.
Vault
Pine
Oh, I think I got it.
Wait, it already flew away even now.
Pine by pine
Matsuzakaya
Oh, is that right?
Yes!
Matsuzakaya?
Yuzu always wins.
So work a little harder.
You don't have any variety.
You can win.
We're doing it wrong.
Yeah, and we're all blabbermouths.
There's a bonus code this time.
That we're doing something we don't even know we're doing
That we didn't even know we were doing could lead to bonus points.
But it doesn't matter if it's just one point.
Um, no, no, no, no.
It's 3 points.
Ta-da!
I reacted in a humble way, like I'm not ready for the green car yet.
I think everyone said "Yay!
Did you know? Did you know?
I'm sending you a happy birthday message, Arline!
Yes!
Yay!
You're still the same.
No, it's not.
We're all just up here together.
Next stop, this way!
We were the first to arrive at the morning meeting time.
Wow...
Yuzujan!
Good morning.
It's already spinning.
You shoot from here?
Yes. Thank you.
You make a good impression.
I do quite a bit of mascarnate.
I lose my energy in the morning.I lose my energy in the morning.
I knew it.
Yes, congratulations.
Congratulations!
It's raining.
Why are you depressed?
The last thing I can't always say
You're always late.
You're always late
He's always late
Yay!
Congratulations!
Look! Look at that! The color is just right!
I guess it's luck.
Lucky.
I shouldn't have come so early.
Hey, wait! What is it?
Yuzu, give me a minus.
Do something.
Yuzu wins!
We're all going home together.
And we all want to go home together and eat sujote.
I don't want to eat Sujote by myself.
I'm looking forward to eating Sujote with everyone!
The group that doesn't sell well is more comfortable in a standard car.
What am I supposed to do in the green car?
Shake an udon and there's a blue one on the floor.
I can't sleep!
Ta-da!
So...
We're all in the coach.
What's that?
Two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Let's all make a final toast.
Huh?
Cheers!